A Guide to the Papers of Emily Couric, ca. 1983-2002
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Emily Couric ca. 1983-2002
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
12986, 12986-a
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection arrived in two phases; the first group (MSS 12986) was given by Dr. George Beller, Charlottesville, Virginia, on March 20, 2004. The second group (MSS 12986-a) was given by Tracy Eppard, from the office of Creigh Deeds, Charlottesville, Virginia, on March 14, 2005. The two groups were considered as a unit and have been interfiled under the original accession number (MSS 12986), with a single guide and box arrangement.
Biographical/Historical Information
Emily Couric (1947-2001) was elected to the Virginia Senate in 1995 and 1999, representing the 25th Senate District of the Commonwealth of Virginia, consisting of Charlottesville, Albemarle County, Madison County, Green County, and parts of Nelson County and Orange County. Couric also served as the Chairwoman of the Democratic Party of Virginia, and was preparing for a campaign for lieutenant governor in 2001 when she was diagnosed with cancer.
She served on the boards of several organizations, including the Jefferson Area Board for the Aging, Boys & Girls Club, Camp Holiday Trails and the Sustainability Council for the Thomas Jefferson Planning District, as well as chairman of the Charlottesville School Board, where she served for six years.
Couric began her career as a high school biology teacher in Cambridge, Massachusetts (1969-1971) and worked for the U.S. Department of the Interior, Fish & Wildlife Service (1971-1973), the U.S. Department of Labor (1974-1978), and as a reporter for Legal Times, Washington, D.C. (1979-1981). Until she began her service in the Virginia Senate, she worked as a writer, publishing in a variety of law-related and general interest publications. She also published two books with St. Martin's Press pertaining to the law, The Trial Lawyers and Divorce Lawyers.
She was born in Atlanta, Georgia, on June 5, 1947, and moved to Virginia in 1951, graduating from Yorktown High School, Arlington, Virginia, in 1965. Couric attended Smith College and graduated in 1969, magna cum laude and Phi Beta Kappa. At the time of her death, she was married to Dr. George A. Beller and had two sons, Ray and Jeff, from a previous marriage.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the papers of Virginia State Senator Emily Couric (1947-2001), ca. 1983-2002, ca. 20,000 items (80 Hollinger boxes, 33.5 linear shelf feet). The collection consists of files regarding Emily Couric's legislation in the Virginia General Assembly; constituent mail and replies; her Virginia Senate campaigns in 1995 and 1999, as well as her initial steps toward declaring candidacy for lieutenant governor; speeches; and files of media appearances (newspaper and magazine articles, audio and Videotapes). Some personal correspondence is present. The largest groups of material in the legislative issues series reflect her interests in issues pertaining to education and health.
Arrangement
Series I: Legislative Issues and Files (Boxes 1-45) Series II: Campaigns (Boxes 46-64) Subseries A: 1995 Campaign (Boxes 46-51) Subseries B: 1999 Campaign (Boxes 51-62) Subseries C: Lt. Governor Campaign (Boxes 63-64) Series III: Administrative Files (Boxes 65-68) Series IV: Constituent Mail (Boxes 69-78) Series V: Speeches (Boxes 79-80) Series VI: Audiovisual Materials (only materials in 12986-a) Subseries A. Legislative Subseries B. Couric for Senate Subseries C. Other Politics Subseries D. Presentation and Demo Reels Subseries E. Memorial and Tributes Subseries F. National Television Subseries G. Miscellaneous Subseries H. Public Television Subseries I. Medical Subseries J. Politics General Subseries K. Debates
Contents List
- Series I: Legislative Issues and Files
  - Affirmative Action, 1999 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Aging- Emily Couric's Day for Seniors, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Agriculture- On-farm Sales, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Agriculture- On-farm Sales, 1997-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Albemarle County- Department of Social Services, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Albemarle County- Medical Society, 1999 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Albemarle County- Tax Surplus, 2000 (Box-folder 1:7)
  - Alcoholic Beverages, 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Amber Warning Lights for Bicycle Races, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Armenian Genocide, 2000 (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Armenian Genocide, n.d. (Box-folder 1:11)
  - Ashlawn Highland Festival, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - Ashlawn Highland Festival- Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 1:13)
  - Assisted Suicide, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Athletics- Title IX, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Blue Ridge Architectural Craft Center, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Benefits for Town Council Member (SB 956), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Board of Zoning Appeals, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Bonus Tags for Deer (SB 674), 1998 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Brain Injury Association of Virginia (BIAV)- Sales Tax Exemption, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Budget Amendments, 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Charitable Gaming Commission (SB 426), 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Charlottesville- Albemarle County- Drug Courts, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Charlottesville- Albemarle County- SPCA, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2:11)
  - Charlottesville Area School Business Alliance (CASBA), 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Charlottesville- Garrett Square Apartments, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 2:13)
  - Charlottesville- Garrett Square Apartments, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 2:14)
  - Charlottesville High School Orchestra, 1999 (Box-folder 2:15)
  - Charlottesville Municipal Board- Municipal Arts Center, 2000 (Box-folder 2:16)
  - Charlottesville- Reversion Controversy, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Charlottesville- Reversion Controversy, 1997, n.d. (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Charlottesville- University Village Condominium, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Charlottesville- West Main Street Development, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Child Abuse, 1995, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Child Day Care, 1996-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Child Day Care Council, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Children, 1993,1997-1998 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Christian Aid Mission Property Tax Exemption, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Christian Coalition, 1997 (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Clinch Valley College Name Change to University of Virginia- Wise, 1999 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Commissioners of Accounts, 2000 (Box-folder 3:12)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI), 1989-1997 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI), 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI) SB 484, 1997 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI) SB 484, 1998 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI) SB 484, 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Ad Hoc- Advisory Group, 1994-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Advisory Board, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Advocacy Organization, 1996-2002, n.d. (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Final Bill 1997, 1997 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Funding Request 1998, 1996-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Implementation, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Commonwealth Neurotrama Initiative (CNI)- Trust Fund, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Community Plans and Funding, 1995, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Compensation and Benefits for State Legislators, 1998 (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Compensation and Benefits for State Legislators, 1999 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Computer Reclamation, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5:9)
  - Computers for Kids Program, 1999 January-April (Box-folder 5:10)
  - Computers for Kids Program, 1999 May-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Confederate Heritage Month, 1997, 1999 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Consumer Credit Reporting (SB 971), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Continuing Care Retirement Communities (CCRCs), 1999-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Court Clerks, 1998 (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Crime- Compensation for Forensic Experts (SB 850), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Crime- Graffiti Threats (SB 847), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Crime- Juvenile, 1993-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Crime- Marital Sexual Assault Task Group, 1984-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Crime- Peeing Tom Loophole, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Crime- Prison Reform, 1991-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Crime- Sexual Battery Bill (SB 939), 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Coyote Bounty, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Credit Card Scam, 1998 (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Crop Tech Corporation, Blacksburg, Virginia, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Cultural Facilities Bond Bill, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Death Penalty, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Death Penalty, 1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Department of Environmental Quality- Over Payment, 1997 (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Department of Environmental Quality- Restructuring, 1997 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles- Front-end License Plate Waiver, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles- Illegally Tinted Windows, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles- Special License Plates (SB 123), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles- Special License Plates Study, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles- Water Damaged Vehicles, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Department of Social Services- Child Protective Services Staffing Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 7:15)
  - Department of Social Services- Foster Care and Adoption at Local Offices, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 7:16)
  - Department of Social Services- Foster Care and Adoption- Budget Amendment, 1998 (Box-folder 7:17)
  - Department of Social Services- Sonia Rivero, 2001 (Box-folder 7:18)
  - Deputy Sheriffs' Retirement, 2000 (Box-folder 7:19)
  - Development Impact Fees, 1993-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 7:20)
  - Drought, 1999 (Box-folder 7:21)
  - Drunk Driving Statute, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 7:22)
  - Education- Advanced Mathematics and Technology Diploma (SB 706), 1999 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Education- Advanced Mathematics and Technology Diploma (SB 706), 2000 (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Education- Advanced Mathematics and Technology Diploma (SB 706), n.d. (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Education- Advancement Via Individual Determination- Charlottesville, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Education- After- School Program Funded by State Farm, 2000 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Education- Agricultural Curriculum Specialists, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Education- Alternative, 1995-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Education- Alternative Licensure, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Education- Automatic Expulsion for Juvenile Offenders (SB 362), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Education- Charter Schools, 1995- 1997 (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Education- Charter Schools, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Education- Charter Schools- Reports, n.d. (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Education- Charter Schools- Reports, n.d. (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Education- Charter Schools- Special Subcommittee, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Education- Charter Schools- Special Subcommittee, 1994-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education- August 28, 1998, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education- November 18,1998, 1998 (Box-folder 9:8)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education- January 14, 1999, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Education Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education (HJR 226) Citizen's Advisory Task Force- August 21, 1998, 1998 (Box-folder 9:10)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education (HJR 226) Citizen's Advisory Task Force- September 23, 1998, 1994-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 9:11)
  - Education- Commission on Access and Diversity in Higher Education (HJR 226) Citizen's Advisory Task Force- October 23, 1998, 1998 (Box-folder 9:12)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education, 1998 (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- Budget Amendments, 1998 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- Budget Amendments for House Bills, 1998 (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- Business and Education Partnerships (SB 168), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- Educational Opportunities (SB 167), 1998 (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- Excellence in Public Schools (SB 165), 1998 (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- General Legislation, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education- Report, 1998 (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education Senate Bills (Notebook), 1998 (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Education- Commission on the Future of Public Education-Training and Professional Development (SB 166), 1998 (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Education- Communities in Schools, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Education- Early Intervention Reading Initiative- Budget Amendment, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 10:12)
  - Education- Educational Needs of Certain Underserved Gifted Students Joint Subcommittee (HJR 251)- September 21, 1998, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 10:13)
  - Education- Educational Needs of Certain Underserved Gifted Students Joint Subcommittee (HJR 251)- December 7, 1998, 1998 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Education- Educational Needs of Certain Underserved Gifted Students Joint Subcommittee (HJR 251)- January 12, 1999, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Education- Equal Educational Opportunity and Diversity Incentive Grants Program (SB 602), 1998 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Education- Fine Arts, 1998 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Education Funding, 1989-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Education Funding- Composite Index, 1996-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Education- Goals 2000, 1995-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Education- Governor's School, 1997 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Education- High Schools That Work1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Education- Higher Education, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Education- Higher Education, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Education- Home Schooling, 1990-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Education- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Remedial Summer School Program (HJR 62)- January 4, 1999, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Education- Joint Subcommittee Studying the Remedial Summer School Program (HJR 62)- January 13, 1999, 1999 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Education- Joint Subcommittee Studying Remediation (HJR 572)- September 2, 1999, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Education- Joint Subcommittee Studying Remediation (HJR 572)- November 10, 1999, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Education- Joint Subcommittee Studying Remediation (HJR 572)- January 11, 2000, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Education- Labor Day Law, 1993-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Education- Middle School, 1997-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Education- New Horizons Regional Education Center, 1997-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Education- Newspapers, 2000 (Box-folder 12:10)
  - Education- Personal Living and Finances Bill (SB 527), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 12:11)
  - Education- Piedmont Regional Education Program, 1999 (Box-folder 12:12)
  - Education- Plan for Better Education, 1995, 1997, n.d. (Box-folder 12:13)
  - Education- Problem of Student Drinking, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 12:14)
  - Education- Project LEAP (Learning Experiences Assessing Potential), n.d. (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Education- Public, 1994-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Education- Pupil-Teacher Ratios, 1992, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Education- RE-SEED Project, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Education- Retired Teachers- Reemployment (SB 146), 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Education- Retired Teachers (SB 954), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Education- Retired Teachers (SB 954)- Amendment, 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Education- School Construction / Lottery Proceeds, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Education- School Construction / Lottery Proceeds, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 13:9)
  - Education- School Construction-Greene and Orange Counties, Va., including classroom trailers. Photographs and Negatives, 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 13:10)
  - Education- School Guidance Counselors, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Education- School Nurses and Student Health, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Education- School Nurses and Student Health, 1998-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Education- School-To-Work Opportunities Act of 1994, 1994-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Education- School Safety, 1987, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Education- School Safety, 1999-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Education- School Safety (Local Schools), 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Education- Special Education, 1996-2000 n.d. (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Education- Standards of Learning, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Education- Standards of Learning, 2000 (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Education-Standards of Learning, 2001, n.d. (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Education- Standards of Learning- Raising Student Achievement: K- 12 Education Reform Update, 1998 October 1 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Education- Standards of Learning- Sample Tests, n.d. (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Education- Teacher Licensure, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Education- Teacher Licensure, 1999 (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Education- Teacher Licensure, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Education- Teacher Salaries, 1997-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Education- Teacher Tenure (SB 122), 1997 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Education- Teacher Tenure (SB 122), 1998 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Education- Teacher Tenure (SB 232), 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Education- Technology, 1995-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 16:7)
  - Education- Truancy, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 16:8)
  - Education- Tuition Cut, 1998 (Box-folder 16:9)
  - Education- Virginia First and Till Hazel, 1995 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Education- Virginia School Boards Association- Attorney General Opinions, 1998 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Education- Virginia Teaching Scholarship Loan Program (Eligibility of Paraprofessionals), 2000 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Education- Vocation, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Elections and Voting- Polling Bill, 1995 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Elections and Voting- Motor Voter Registration, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Electric Utility Restructuring, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Employment- Termination due to Pregnancy, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 17:8)
  - Employment- Work Force Training, 2000 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - Employment- Work Force Transition Act, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17:10)
  - Employment- Work Source Enterprises, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 17:11)
  - Environment- Hog Farming, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 17:12)
  - Environment- Importation of Trash, 1997-1998 September (Box-folder 17:13)
  - Environment- Importation of Trash, 1998 October-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 17:14)
  - Environment- Importation of Trash- Memorializing Congress Resolution, 1999 (Box-folder 17:15)
  - Environment- Ivy Landfill, Albemarle County, 1984-1995 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Environment- Ivy Landfill, Albemarle County, 1996 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Environment- Ivy Landfill, Albemarle County, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Environment- Ivy Landfill, Albemarle County, 1999 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Environment- Ivy Landfill, Albemarle County, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Environment- Leaking Underground Storage Tanks, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Environment- Montebello Clean Mountain Coalition, 1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Environment- Open Space Preservation, 1996-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Environment- Poultry Farming Wastes, 1994-1998 February (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Environment- Poultry Farming Wastes, 1998-1998 March-December (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Environment- Poultry Farming Wastes, 1999-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 19:5)
  - Environment- Power Plants, 2000 (Box-folder 19:6)
  - Environment- Power Plants Permitting in Virginia (SB 1030), 1999-2001 (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Environment- Power Plants Permitting in Virginia (SB 1030)- Piedmont Environmental Council Packet, 2001 (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Environment- Upper Rapidan River Tier III Designation, 2001 (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Environment- Wetlands Protection, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Farmer's Market, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Floods, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Floods- Hurricane Fran Disaster Relief, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Forensic Psychologists, 2001 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Frontier Culture Museum- Pig Slaughter Controversy, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Gambling, 1995-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Garden Club, 1999 (Box-folder 20:8)
  - Gay/Lesbian Issues, 2000 (Box-folder 20:9)
  - Greene County, 1994-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 20:10)
  - Greene County Loop Trail Project, 1996 (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Greene County- Middle River Hurricane Fran Flooding, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 20:12)
  - Greene County- Regulation of Parking (SB 958), 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 20:13)
  - Greene County- School Boards (SB 1369), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 20:14)
  - Greene County Senior Center/ Library- Budget Amendment, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 20:15)
  - Gun Control, 1993-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 20:16)
  - Health- Aging, 1996- 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Health- Alternative Medicine, 1995-2000, n.d. (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Health- Alzheimer's Association Rural Caregiver Support Initiative, n.d. (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Health Care, 1995-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Health- Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Health- Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan- Children and Health Insurance- Making the Connection, n.d. (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Health- Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan- Implementation, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - Health- Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan- Implementation, 1999 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - Health- Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan- Implementation, 2000-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 21:9)
  - Health- Children's Specialty Services, 1999 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Health- Clinical Trials for Life Threatening Diseases, 1990-1992, 1998 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Health- Clinical Trials for Life Threatening Diseases, 1999 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Health- Clinical Trials for Life Threatening Diseases, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Health- Collaborative Practice Agreements, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening- American College of Gastroenterology, 2000 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening Coverage (SB 1285 and SB 26), 1990, 1998 (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening Coverage (SB 1285 and SB 26), 1999 January (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening Coverage (SB 1285 and SB 26), 1999 March-November (Box-folder 22:9)
  - Health- Colorectal Cancer Screening Coverage (SB 1285 and SB 26), 2000 January- March (Box-folder 22:10)